export const QNA = {
  ko: [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "행사 신청은 어떻게 하나요?",
      answer:
        "행사 신청은 Festa 주소 https://festa.io/events/3435 에서 티켓을 발권하고 있습니다, 만약 구매가 어려우시면 현장에서도 발권을 도와드리니 행사 일정에 현장에서 등록하셔도 됩니다.",
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: "주차장 지원 되나요?",
      answer:
        "현장에서의 주차 지원은 어렵습니다, 따라서 가급적 대중교통을 이용하시기를 권장드리며, 만약 자가용 차량 이용시 근처 유료주차장을 이용하시기 바랍니다. (* 주차장 정보는 Festa 행사 페이지 참고)",
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: "참석 확인증 수령 가능할까요?",
      answer:
        "참석 확인증은 gophercon.kor@gmail.com 이메일이나 https://pf.kakao.com/_wnrqG 을 이용하여 문의주시면, PDF 형태로 보내드릴 수 있으며, 혹은 Festa 상에서 티켓의 체크인 상태를 증빙자료로 사용하실 수도 있습니다.",
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: "굿즈는 2일 모두 참가하면, 언제 수령받게 되나요?",
      answer: "굿즈는 8월 5일 혹은 6일 중, 가장 첫번째로 참석한 날 수령 받게 되며, 그 이후 중복 수령이 어렵습니다.",
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: "점심 식사가 제공되나요?",
      answer:
        "네, 점심 식사와 커피 케이터링 서비스가 제공되며, 현장에서 간단한 샌드위치와 음료를 수령하실 수 있습니다.",
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: "행사 자료나 다시보기가 제공되나요?",
      answer:
        "네, 추후 행사 녹화본에 대해서 제공됩니다. 다만 현장 만큼의 상호작용이나 질의응답 등이 불가능한 점 참고 부탁드립니다.",
    },
  ],
  en: [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "How do I apply for an event?",
      answer:
        "Tickets for the event are being issued at the Festa address https://festa.io/events/3435, but if you can't make it, we'll be on hand to help with ticketing, so you can sign up for the event on-site.",
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: "Is parking supported?",
      answer:
        "Parking is not available, so we suggest using public transportation if possible, and if you have a car, please use the nearby paid parking lots. (*Please refer to the Festa event page for parking information.)",
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: "Can I get a confirmation of attendance?",
      answer:
        "Confirmation of attendance can be sent to you in PDF format by emailing gophercon.kor@gmail.com or https://pf.kakao.com/_wnrqG, or you can use your ticket's check-in status on Festa as proof of attendance.",
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: "If I attend both days, when will I receive my swags?",
      answer:
        "You will receive your swags on August 5 or 6, whichever comes first, and you will not be able to claim it after that.",
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: "Is lunch provided?",
      answer: "Yes, lunch and coffee catering is available, and you can pick up light sandwiches and drinks on site.",
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: "Will there be event materials or a replay?",
      answer:
        "Yes, a recording of the event will be available afterward. However, please note that it will not allow for the same level of interaction and Q&A as the live event.",
    },
  ],
};
